[{"answer": "Gosh.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Fifteen million albums or big talent show superstar?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Not necessarily.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Did you worry that if it didn't do that well it could damage the Maroon 5 end of things?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Have you been surprised about how your profile has changed since the smash hit of \"The Voice\"?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Not so -- well, a little bit.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Did you all feel the competitive juices coming out?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "You can -- well, do either actually, because you know who they are.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Do I have to turn my chair around or I have to mentor them?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "She's ridiculous.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "What would your reaction be?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Great singer.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Justin Bieber?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "He could.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Could he win \"The Voice\"?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Given the right circumstances, probably.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Could she win a show like \"The Voice\"?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Secret Adam Levine -- you know, I was all in with music.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "What are the secret Adam Levine talents we don't know about?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I can balance things on my nose pretty well.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Weird little party pieces you do?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "I can balance a lot of stuff on my nose.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "How big a thing can you balance on your nose?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Could I go down here?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, you can definitely come back.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "If I do, do I get like 15 bucks or something?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "ORGAN: Have you ever performed this stunt live on television?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "It is a two-way street.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "But thank God we've got somebody in the music business who recognizes it's a two-way street, isn't it?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Do the paparazzi give you a hard time?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "I've never played naked Twister.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Did you play naked Twister, Adam?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I just thought it was a funny Tweet.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "You'd like to, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "It's exciting, you know, especially for us.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "When we saw Prince William and -- or the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge, as they are now, in Hollywood recently, what did you make of all the fuss that came with them?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "I like they like the romantic kind of idea behind it.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Why do the Americans like the royals so much?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Star struck.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Who have you been star struck by?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Who have you been most excited -- I mean, you're a massive Beatles fan, right?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Have you met Paul McCartney?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Paul McCartney, I'd really like to meet you.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "If Paul McCartney's watching, you're available, yes?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Not miserable at all.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "I mean, how miserable can that particular vignette be, Adam?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Percentage-wise.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "That's an alleged list?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I met her -- I'm not telling that story.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Where did you meet Anna?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "It's not bad.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "How bad is it?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Millions of men are always trying to sleep with her, so it works itself out.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "How does she deal with the cliche' of millions of women freaking out when they see you?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "It's pretty even.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Who gets more jealous?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Heavy drug regimen.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "How have you managed to avoid that kind of pitfall?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Oh, so many people.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Who do you have that would do that to you?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "I think I've found balance, you know, through family and through friends and through really wonderful people in my life.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Is it from your parents, your family?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "I want to start having kids, yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Not necessarily.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "ORGAN: Do you believe you should be married to do that?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "My friend Sean Taya (ph) actually.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Whose marriage has inspired you?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Just being very close with him and to the whole thing and actually his daughter's my god daughter and I've seen just the right type of marriage in the two of them.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Why do you think it works so well?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Professionally --", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Where would you like to be professionally?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Producing records.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Other than working less?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "To make a plan would be really foolish.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Or could you go solo for example?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Well, I'd love to beat the odds.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Isn't there always the point where you all just get sick of each other?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "EVINE: We drive each other crazy.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "How's the scale of irritation with band members right now?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Adam Levine, you're disgusting.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Who knew that?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Well, what I mean about it is more in being real and being honest and being your authentic self.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "What do you mean by this?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I said yes.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "How did you -- how did you answer that?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "We actually did play a lot of Guns and Roses when we worked out together.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "You and Charlie hang out to that one?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "No, not self-destruction.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "You had a slight appetite yourself for self-destruction over the years, do you think?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "For destruction?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Did you see that interview?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "I really -- I thought it was a great interview.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "What did you think of it?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "He was amazing.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "What was he like when you first got together with him?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Do I talk to Charlie?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Today's a good day.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Today's a good day?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "I take it day by day.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Is that how it works?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "We've had a good stretch now, which is nice.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "Do you know immediately if it's a good or bad day?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Is he in a better place now?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "I think it's not about he and I truly.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "And how have you managed that, do you think?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "I have a lot of male friends.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "True?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "If Charlie was to sort his life out, could you ever imagine a scenario where you might one day get back together or not?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "That door is closed.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "That door's closed?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "At the time I did.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "Did you care or not?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "Well, it was -- it's very overwhelming.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "What was it like being a Hollywood starlet?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "Do you still love acting?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "I turned 40 this year.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "But I know you're older than you look, which is always the best answer, right?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "Clean living.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "How do you stay so youthful?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "Clean living.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "Clean living?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "In some ways, yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Did you find it cathartic doing the book?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Do you think?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "I think people that meet me see that I'm who I am.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "I mean, does it carry with it a tricky stigma, or have you been able to say no, this is me now?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "Oh, I've learned to look for -- the qualities that I look for now are different than prior to getting married and having kids.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 799, "question": "What have you learned to look for that suits you?", "qSentId": 798}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 805, "question": "Is motherhood, to you, your greatest achievement?", "qSentId": 804}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "Can you lead a relatively normal life now?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "I would definitely encourage them to do whatever they wanted.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 818, "question": "If they said, mom, we really want to go into acting, given all that you've been through, would you encourage them or would you be slightly reticent about that?", "qSentId": 817}, {"answer": "That would be fair.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 831, "question": "Would that be fair?", "qSentId": 830}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 840, "question": "Is this something that's been on your mind?", "qSentId": 839}, {"answer": "She's amazing.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 862, "question": "And how is she?", "qSentId": 861}, {"answer": "She's a month.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 864, "question": "How old is she now?", "qSentId": 863}, {"answer": "They are so in love with her.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 871, "question": "What do your other kids make of her?", "qSentId": 870}, {"answer": "I've had many loves.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 898, "question": "Do you believe you're going to fall in love again?", "qSentId": 897}, {"answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 910, "question": "You remain optimistic?", "qSentId": 909}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 913, "question": "Are you quite excited about that prospect?", "qSentId": 912}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 923, "question": "What next for you in terms of maybe acting?", "qSentId": 922}, {"answer": "With Quentin Tarantino.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 928, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 927}, {"answer": "I have to say, the last few years it's like something always happens right before my interviews that's in the headlines.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 941, "question": "Do you enjoy the interview process or not?", "qSentId": 940}, {"answer": "There were times I did, yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 949, "question": "Do you feel sometimes -- when you see all the magazines and stuff, do you feel like you're a soap opera character, not a real person?", "qSentId": 948}, {"answer": "This isn't that hurtful, but it's weird, that I used to be a hooker, I used to be a Heidi Fleiss girl.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 955, "question": "What was the worst story that you've had to -- that you've seen that's just completely untrue, but most hurtful to you?", "qSentId": 954}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 975, "question": "It's the only way, isn't it?", "qSentId": 974}, {"answer": "I just want him to be a very healthy person.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 980, "question": "What would you wish for Charlie?", "qSentId": 979}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110813pmt", "aSentId": 983, "question": "Do you have an optimism that he might sort himself out a bit?", "qSentId": 982}]